Guide to the National Federation of Grain Cooperatives records, 1946-1976.
National Federation of Grain Cooperatives records,
- Series III. Import Quotas
  - Imports of Canadian Grain - Defense Production Act, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, statements, bills, public laws; Roy F. Hendrickson statement (May 29, 1952), 4 pp., tables, mimeo; letters from Congressmen indicating receipt of Roy F. Hendrickson letter on import of grain; reference to article CORNELL LAW REVIEW by Edwin G. Martin on trade agreements and price supports, (ca. 1951-1952); Roy F. Hendrickson to M.W. Thatcher (Jun 6, 1952) on amendments where H spells out why amendments lost; see also Roy F. Hendrickson to Mr. James R. Bliss, Lansing, Michigan
  - Imports of Canadian Barley, 1954-01-19 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson 9pp., tables, mimeo, 3 copies
  - Imports of Canadian Grain, 1954-09-15 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson 8 pp., tables, 2 copies
  - Imports of Canadian Grain, 1954-04-07 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson, Senate Agriculture Committee, 7 pp., mimeo, 3 copies
  - Imports of Canadian Grain, 1953-04-23 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Statement, M.W. Thatcher, 7 pp., Senate Committee on Agriculture and Forestry, 1 copy
  - Imports of Flaxseed and Linseed Oil, 1953-05-07-1953-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson, 2 pp., U.S. Tariff Commission, 1 copy
  - Imports - Mixed Feeds, 1955-05-23 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Roy F. Hendrickson to Marvin L. McLain, Commodity Stabilization Service, USDA, 2 pp.
  - Import Quotas - Oats, Barely, Rye, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, news release includes Milton R. Young (Apr 10, 1954) on barley situation and on the Secretary Henry A. Wallace letter (Feb 1, 1953) which he says "I can make good use of the material contained in the Secretary's letter." also Congressman N. Dakota with USDA
  - Imports of Canadian Oats, 1953-07-07 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson, 10 pp., U.S. Tariff Commission, 1 copy
  - Imports Weed Seeds, 1960-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Statement, Roy F. Hendrickson, 8 pp., Weed Society of America, 1 copy
  - Imports, Screenings, Weed Seed, 1947-1959 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Correspondence on "screenings" include Mr. William H. Gee, Seattle, Washington; USDA 1955 grain screenings; Clifford R. Hope, House, Kansas, 1947 import of grain
  - Imports of Canadian Wheat, Unfit for Human Consumption Report, Bureau of Customs, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Fiscal year ended Jun 30, 1952; relating to importation of Wheat Classified as Unfit for Human Consumption, 16 pp., mimeograph, 2 copies
  - Imports of Wheat Unfit for Human Consumption Statement, 1953-05-26 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Roy F. Hendrickson, 7 pp., mimeograph Senate Committee on Agriculture and Forestry, 1 copy
  - Imports of Canadian Wheat, Unfit for Human Consumption Statement, 1953-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Roy F. Hendrickson, 8 pp., Senate Judiciary Committee, 2 copies
  - Imports … etc. - Prohibiting Commingling, S. 784, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Correspondence on hearings on unfit wheat and the definition of "unfit"; numerous Congressman correspondents; Milton R. Young, Herman Welker, etc.
  - Imports - Tables, 1920-1954 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Mostly information on early 1950s
  - Imports - Wheat and Flour, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Includes "Wheat and Wheat Flour" Report 145, Second Series, U.S. Tariff Commission, Washington
- Series IV. Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA)
  - Storage Policies, Government, Southwest U.S., 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Correspondence, storing grain in Texas; includes Frank M. Phariss, Producers Grain Corporation, Amarillo (Jan 7, 1966) to Roy F. Hendrickson, personal storage, 2 pp.
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Correspondence, forms, reports, tables on storage of grain; Farmers Grain Dealers Association of Iowa; Cooperative Marketing Association, Kansas City, Missouri; Union Equity Co-Operative Exchange, Oklahoma; Westcentral Cooperative Grain Company, Omaha
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA)- Syminton Investigating Committee, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Includes reports and statements; Roy F. Hendrickson statement; about 15 pp. of tables
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Reports of Proceedings, Committee of Investigation, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, grain storage with committee and USDA
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Proceedings, Vol 2., 1960-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Draft Report of Syminton Subcommittee, Grain Storage (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Reports and statements on hearings, Hubert H. Humphrey to Roy F. Hendrickson on Syminton Subcommittee
  - Senate Agriculture Committee - Investigation of Grain Storage, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Clippings, various newspapers
  - Grain Storage, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Correspondence on grain storage; includes carbon copies and other copies concerning M.W. Thatcher, Roy F. Hendrickson, Hubert H. Humphrey, James G. Patton, and Charles F. Brannan all on Syminton Subcomittee
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Rate schedules
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Final and Proposed, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Includes drafts and final copies
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    USDA announcements
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Correspondence and minutes
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Minutes, meeting, Kansas City; also statements, as Grain and Feed Dealers
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960-01-1960-04 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Newsletters, Roy F. Hendrickson comments
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Correspondence; includes J. Frank, Producers Grain Corporation, Amarillo; W.A. Richards, North Pacific Grain Growers, Inc., A. Price Feuquay, Enid, Oklahoma; William F. Brooks, National Grain Trade Council; P.J. Nash, Farmers Union Jobbing Association, Kansas City, Missouri
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) Statements, Reports, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Fred Maywald Correspondence; F.M., Manager, Farmers Grain Dealers Association, Des Moines
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Commodity Credit Corporation, Storage Cost Figures, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, reports, etc.; some correspondence on Syminton Subcommittee Investigation
  - Grain Storage - Syminton Subcommittee (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Correspondence and clippings; Kansas, Nebraska
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Syminton Subcommittee, 1959-12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Government Accountability Office Report
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Proceedings, Vol 1., Syminton Subcommittee, 1960-01-12 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, statements, Syminton Subcommittee
  - Farmers Grain Dealers Association, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Fred Maywald correspondence; also some Congressional correspondence; Don L. Short, N. Dakota; Catherine May, Washington
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1954-1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Guy M. Gillette, Senator, Iowa
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Commodity Credit Corporation, Cost Survey, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Proceedings, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Mimeograph, grain storage, USDA, 3 vols.
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1951-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, reports, tables
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, reports, drafts on proposed storage provisions
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, newsletters, tables, concerning storage; Oregon, Ohio, Iowa, National Farmers Union; interesting letters between Wes McCune, Farmers Union, and Roy H. Hendrickson on storage and Syminton Committee
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, newsletters, reports
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, reports; letters from Nebraska, Texas, and Kansas cooperatives
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Reports, hearings, statements
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA), 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Concerning USDA, correspondence, reports
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Congressional Records and Appropriations Bill, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Bills, drafts of legislation, statements
  - Uniform Grain Storage Agreement (UGSA) - Martin Abrahamsen, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Series V. Assorted Materials
  - Adomeit, Bernard L. - Illinois Grain Corporation, Letter to Roy F. Hendrickson, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Aeration of Grain in Commercial Storage - Proceedings, 1 Vol, Ames, Iowa, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Adjustment Act, USDA, Agriculture Handbook No. 49, 1953-01-01 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Outlook Conference, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Papers presented by staff, USDA, mimeograph
  - "Agricultural Policy in an Affluent Society" by Vernon W. Ruttan, University of Minnesota, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Andrews, Stanley - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Between Andrews, Alamo, Texas, and Roy F. Hendrickson
  - Antitrust Hearings, S. 2014, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Statements, bills, correspondence on hearings
  - Antitrust Cooperatives, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, press news release, clippings, draft statement by Oriville Freeman
  - Antitrust Maryland - Virginia Milk Producers, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Clippings, news release
  - Appalachian Region Program, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Bills, news release
  - Agricultural Appropriations, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Bills, congressional record, statement regarding appropriations
  - Appropriations, USDA - Farm Credit Administration, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Bills
  - Appropriations, USDA - Whitten Report, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Jamie L. Whitten, House, Mississippi; other Congressmen and cooperatives from Minnesota; also, Roy F. Hendrickson, National Grain Trade Council
  - Appropriations, USDA - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Argentine Cooperative Officials - Arrangements for Luncheon, 1965-10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Association of American Executives - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Association of American Railroads - Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Baker, George P. - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bank for Cooperatives, IRS and Class C Stocks, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Correspondence
  - Bank for Cooperatives - Budget Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Correspondence and statements, Roy F. Hendrickson; National Grain, Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, Jerry Voorhis, Farm Credit Administration
  - Bank for Cooperatives - Farm Credit Act of 1955, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Hearings, bills, correspondence
  - Bank for Cooperatives - Farm Credit Act of 1955 (continued), 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Bills, reports, hearings
  - Bank for Cooperatives - Legislation, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Reports, statements, memos, correspondence
  - Bank for Cooperatives - Reports and Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    National Farmers Union, Iowa Farmers Union, M.W. Thatcher
  - Barter Program, USDA - Statements, 1957-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bartlett, Arthur C., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, clippings; letter from Roy F. Hendrickson to Arthur Barlett (Jul 27, 1964); mention of Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C.
  - Bean, Louis H. - Economic Consultant, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bean Growers Association of California - Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft - Secretary of Agriculture, 1952-1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, clippings, news releases; Milton Eisenhower to Roy F. Henrickson; RFH (1953) suggests appointees to Benson
  - Benson, Ezra Taft - Secretary of Agriculture, 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Press releases and clippings
  - Bicknell, George R., 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Cooperative Marketing Association, Kansas City, Missouri; correspondence
  - Bird, John - Saturday Evening Post, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Letter from Roy F. Hendrickson on Bird editorial
  - Bjornson, Val - Minnesota State Treasurer, 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Mutual friends, Roy F. Henrickson outlines his career in one letter
  - Bledsoe, S.B. - Public Relations, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Richard Wilson, Washington Star columnist; column on farm surplus and fact that S.C. Freeman agreed with it
  - Borden, Dr. Morton - Montana State University (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Speech, copy on cooperative
  - Bork, Bill - Kansas, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Ran against Bob Dole
  - Boxcar supply, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Correspondence and figures; includes Association of American Railroads, cooperatives in Illinois, Ohio, Minnesota, Nebraska, Colorado, Kansas, Utah; Congressmen Hugh Butler, Edwin C. Johnson
  - Boxcar supply - Legislation, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, bills; Senators John A. Carroll, Richard L. Neuberger; Gordon Allott
  - Brannan, Charles F., 1950-03 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Clippings and speech of Secretary of Agriculture
  - Brannan Plan, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Clippings and articles
  - Brooks, D.W. - Cotton Producers Association, Atlanta, Georgia, 1963-03-15 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Letter to Roy F. Hendrickson on peanuts and cooperatives
  - Brooks, William F. - National Grain Trade Council, 1961-1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Budd, Norval G - Grange League Federation, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Sam Stratton, Roy F. Hendrickson
  - Bulgar, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Calvelage, Hubert B. - Ohio Job Opportunities, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Northern Pacific Grain Growers, Inc., 1951-1962 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Correspondence on weather, crops, politics, agricultural situation
  - Canadian Wheat Board, 1950-1960 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Printed reports
  - Canadian Grain Trade Manitoba Wheat Pools, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Canadian Grain Trade Wheat Pools, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, some on storage and handling of grain
  - Caplin, Mortimer, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Report on Tax Treatment of Cooperatives; clippings and notes
  - Carlson, Frank - Kansas, Senator, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Routine, correspondence on Carlson's retirement
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Material report, Report on Agriculture
  - Chambers, J.M., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Report on importation of cordage and twine into the U.S.
  - Chicago Overseas Shipping Association - Shipping on the Great Lakes, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Civil Rights (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Press releases, reports on blacks, blacks and agriculture
  - Cockrane, Dr. Willard W. - University of Minnesota, 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Observations of his work in USDA; correspondence
  - Cooperative for Commercialisation of Farm Products (COES) - Spain, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Barge Rates, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Correspondence and reports
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) -Bins and Bin Sites (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Statistics, reports, correspondence
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Bin Site II, 1950-1960 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Correspondence, reports, telegrams, hearings
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Bin Site Corn Sales, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC), 1936, 1949, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Co-op Competition - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Office Shift, Dallas to Temple Texas, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Competitive Bidding, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Corn Sales, House Small Business Subcommittee, 1966-06 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Publicker Corn Sale, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Corn Sales, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Criticisms, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Frank G. Daniels, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Grain Handling, Commission Houses, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Grain Handling Cooperatives, 1949-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Inventory, 1957, 1964, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Investigation House Appropriations, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Loan Maturity Dates, 1951, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Roy F. Hendrickson to USDA Secretary of Agriculture Brannan and H.D. Godfrey, ASCS
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Price Support, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Correspondence with USDA officials and some information gtom Hutchinson, Kansas
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Program Costs, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    USDA information
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Purchases Donations, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Stratton Grain Company, Milwaukee; news release, correspondence
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - "Reconstruction Program", 1954, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Reports, correspondence, discussion papers
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Sales Policy, 1955-1965 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, reports; Fred Maywald, USDA
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Reseal Program, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, reports, hearings; M.W. Thatcher letters to Secretary of Agriculture Freeman and to Karl Mundt, Milton R. Young, et al.
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Resale Policy, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, reports, memos, NFGC, National Grange
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Resale Policy, Senate Agriculture Committee, 1966-02 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Statements of persons before hearings
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Reseal Grain Warehouses, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    M.W. Thatcher, Hubert H. Humphrey to Roy F. Hendrickson worried over USDA and GTA and rift between Thatcher and Freeman
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Reseal House Hearings, 1967-03 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Statements by various organizations, Grange, NFGC
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Storage, Correspondence with USDA, 1964, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Subsidy-in-kind, 1956, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Clippings, bills
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Subsidy-in-kind Program, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, Hubert H. Humphrey
  - Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC) - Storage, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, Cotton Warehouse Association
  - Export Policy Changes Wheat, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, news releases, news letters
  - F, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Letters to Secretary of Agriculture Freeman (copies)
  - G, 1954, 1962, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - H, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Includes remarks of Hubert Humphrey to NFGC; correspondence with Fred V. Heinkel, Missouri Farmers Association
  - Hellebust, Hal, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Resolutions, telegram
  - Henrickson, Roy F. - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Imports, 1953, 1958, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    USDA, Senator Karl Mundt, correspondence
  - Common Market - Printed Matter and speeches, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Commodity Exchange Authority - Mimeograph Material, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Commodity Exchange Act, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Testimony on the legislation; letter from Representative Thomas Curtis, Missouri
  - Commodity Exchange Act - Legislation Material, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Conference of 100 - Cooperatives, Cooperative League, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Conference of 100 - Correspondence, Meeting Program, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Conference on Cooperatives and the Future, 1963-04 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Correspondence and related items pertaining to the meeting; Secretary of Agriculture Freeman and Senator H. H. Humphrey
  - Conference on Cooperatives and the Future - Workshop Recommendations, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Conference on Cooperatives and the Future - Workshop Material, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Letters and drafts of agendas
  - Congressional Requests - Speeches (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Roy F. Hendrickson prepared for Senator Hubert H. Humphrey and Senator Milton R. Young
  - Conservation Reserve - News Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Construction, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, M.W. Thatcher, Pakistan
  - Cook, Hamilton W, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Reports on Agriculture, Europe
  - Cooley, Harold D., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    New releases
  - Cooper, Owen, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Possible building, American Agriculture Building in D.C.
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, USDA, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Correspondence and memos; notes on forestry cooperatives
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Correspondence and drafts of cooperative criteria
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Correspondence and reports on cooperatives
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Correspondence and reports on use of cooperatives; Dwayne O. Andreas, Farmers Union Grain Terminal Association; Inland Empire Pea Growers Association; Farmers Grain Dealers Association of Iowa
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, reports, agendas; Roy F. Hendrickson to John A. Baker, Assistant Secretary of Agriculture, on cooperatives and KIPLINGER FARM LETTER
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, agendas; Roy F. Hendrickson to Dorothy H. Jacobson, Assistant to the Secretary, USDA, on cooperatives, history, and discussion
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee - National Commission on Food Marketing, Correspondence and Reports, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1961, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    USDA Policy on Cooperatives, Secretary's memo; correspondence and draft statements
  - Cooperative Advisory Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    USDA Policy on Cooperatives; correspondence and reports
  - Cooperative Month, 1965-10 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cooperative Month, 1964-10 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cooperative Consultation Conference, 1960-Jul 1961 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cooperative Consultation Conference, 1959, Aug-Sep 1960 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cooperative Consultation Conference, 1958, Jul 1959 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cooperative Consultation Conference, 1958-07 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Co-Op Digest, 1948-1959 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, printed matter, Ithaca, New York; M.W. Thatcher
  - Grange League Federation (GLF) - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Merger of Eastern and GLF
  - Cooperative, Grange League Federation (GLF), 1954-1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Printed annual reports
  - Cooperative, Grange League Federation (GLF), 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, reports